<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<propertyList date="2014-08-31-00:52:19" username="" password="">
    <residential modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" status="current">
        <agentID>012345</agentID>
        <uniqueID>13883-edmundstreet</uniqueID>
        <isMultiple value="no" />
        <authority value="" />
        <underOffer value="no" />
        <newConstruction />
        <listingAgent id="1">
            <name />
            <telephone type="BH" />
            <telephone type="mobile" />
            <email>david@villarealestate.com.au</email>
            <twitterURL />
            <facebookURL />
            <linkedInURL />
        </listingAgent>
        <price Display="yes">1295000</price>
        <priceView />
        <address Display="yes">
            <subNumber />
            <streetNumber>31</streetNumber>
            <street>Edmund Street</street>
            <suburb>Shelly Beach</suburb>
            <state>Queensland</state>
            <postcode />
            <country>AUS</country>
        </address>
        <municipality />
        <category name="House" />
        <zone />
        <headline>Beautiful Beach House Shelly Beach, Qld</headline>
        <description><![CDATA[It’s all about the lifestyle! Tightly held Shelly Beach is experiencing great sales and the market is definitely turning, so don't miss out!<br><br>A beautiful home that captures fantastic ocean views of the blue Pacific.<br>This is a quality, architectural home featuring 4 generous bedrooms, 3 bathrooms, an outdoor gourmet kitchen and entertaining area, overlooking a sparkling in ground pool that will satisfy al your entertaining aspirations!<br><br>Upstairs is light and airy, with living areas that create beautiful vistas in every direction. Enjoy the gourmet kitchen with stone counters with views north up the coast. Living & dining combination with timber floors all flow onto two large decks that enjoy expansive ocean views. Also upstairs is a luxurious master with ocean views,WIR and ensuite and two more bedrooms and a shared bathroom.<br><br>Downstairs there is another bedroom, bathroom and a two car garage offering lots of storage. The lot is a generous 789 sqm, complimented by a fully enclosed front yard, allowing plenty of room for the family pet, or to kick a ball (or even caravan or boat storage.)<br><br>Just a short stroll away is picturesque Shelly Beach, and an easy five minute walk takes you to the wonderful cafes and restaurants at Moffat Beach. For everything else it's a five minute drive to Caloundra.<br><br>A must inspect and with so many options this is an opportunity not to miss! Please check our open for inspection times or call Linda for for a private inspection on 0427 378 687.<br><br>View:On Appointment<br>Price: Offered at $1,295,000<br><br>Property Summary:<br><br>Category: Luxury Landscaped Acreage<br>Bedrooms:4<br>Bathrooms:3<br>Garage:2<br><br>Floor Plan:Click to Load Tour<br>Land: 790sqm (approx)<br>Close to: Village, Beaches,Cafes<br>Features: Ocean Views, Privacy, Pool]]></description>
        <tenancy>unknown</tenancy>
        <features>
            <bedrooms>4</bedrooms>
            <Bathrooms>3</Bathrooms>
            <toilets>0</toilets>
            <ensuite>0</ensuite>
            <garages>0</garages>
            <carSpaces>0</carSpaces>
            <carports />
            <openSpaces />
            <balcony />
            <livingAreas />
            <poolInGround>1</poolInGround>
            <otherFeatures>Ocean Views, Privacy, Pool</otherFeatures>
        </features>
        <landDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter">790.00</area>
        </landDetails>
        <buildingDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter" of="0.00" />
            <newlyBuilt value="" />
            <energyRating />
        </buildingDetails>
        <furnished />
        <auction date="" />
        <dateAvailable />
        <inspectionTimes />
        <externalLink />
        <miniweb>
            <uri id="1">http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/edmundstreet.htm</uri>
        </miniweb>
        <videoLink href="" />
        <objects>
            <images>
                <img id="m" modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" url="http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/images/williamsstreet1.jpg" format="jpg" />
            </images>
            <document />
        </objects>
    </residential>
    <residential modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" status="current">
        <agentID>012345</agentID>
        <uniqueID>13883-hamiltonhouse</uniqueID>
        <isMultiple value="no" />
        <authority value="" />
        <underOffer value="no" />
        <newConstruction />
        <listingAgent id="1">
            <name />
            <telephone type="BH" />
            <telephone type="mobile" />
            <email>david@villarealestate.com.au</email>
            <twitterURL />
            <facebookURL />
            <linkedInURL />
        </listingAgent>
        <price Display="yes" />
        <priceView />
        <address Display="yes">
            <subNumber />
            <streetNumber>49</streetNumber>
            <street>Toolborough Road</street>
            <suburb>Coolum</suburb>
            <state>Queensland</state>
            <postcode />
            <country>AUS</country>
        </address>
        <municipality />
        <category name="Mansion" />
        <zone />
        <headline>Modern Mansion on Beautiful Acreage Coolum, Qld</headline>
        <description><![CDATA[Hamilton House is a design masterpiece of superior construction and timeless appeal, practical liveable spaces combining modern features with warm intimate retreats.<br><br>Polished concrete floors and sweeping marble staircase in rich chocolate. There is contrasting use of materials iron / concrete and brass softened by warm timbers and textured wallpapers catering for different moods.<br><br>The lighting is amazing with themed spaces. A  media room reminiscent of a French conversation lounge / a gentleman’s card, library room in art deco style. The kitchen & dining in timeless white displaying a non pretentious simplicity.<br><br>Moveable walls of glass opening up the entire home to the outside. A sundrenched grassed pool deck overlooking the Japanese garden and the ranges beyond. A stunningly private country retreat yet only 6 minutes to the crystal clear bays at Coolum Beach.<br><br>• HPM electronic light switching<br>• Air conditioning 44.8kw ducted in living, dining, gallery & kitchen<br><br>• Commercial grade air curtain isolating living zone<br>• Dressing rooms in master & guest suite<br>• Stone kitchen with double dishwasher, integrated fridge /Freezer<br><br>• Instant filtered boiling & chilled water<br><br>• Commercial exhaust / induction cook top<br>• Grand marble staircase with polished brass balustrading<br>• Commercial grade stacker & bi fold doors<br>• Feature open fire place with joinery wood stack and bar unit<br>• Tranquil Japanese garden with water feature & meditation area<br>• Water supply 129.000 L with triple filtration<br>• 1 million litre Dam w/ pump system for irrigation<br><br>• 11.000litreL tank for gardens surrounding house<br><br>There are not many properties that come close to offering the enormous array of extra touches that make this home truely unique.<br><br>View: On Appointment<br>Price: Expressions of Interest<br><br>Property Summary:<br><br>Category: Luxury Landscaped Acreage<br>Bedrooms:5<br>Bathrooms:5<br>Garage:8<br><br>Land: 8 acres (approx)<br>Close to: Village, Beaches, Transport<br>Features: Resort Pool, Open Fireplace, Privacy, Level Parcel]]></description>
        <tenancy>unknown</tenancy>
        <features>
            <bedrooms>5</bedrooms>
            <Bathrooms>5</Bathrooms>
            <toilets>0</toilets>
            <ensuite>0</ensuite>
            <garages>0</garages>
            <carSpaces>0</carSpaces>
            <carports />
            <openSpaces />
            <balcony />
            <livingAreas />
            <poolInGround>1</poolInGround>
            <otherFeatures>Resort Pool, Open Fireplace, Privacy, Level Parcel</otherFeatures>
        </features>
        <landDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter">0.00</area>
        </landDetails>
        <buildingDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter" of="0.00" />
            <newlyBuilt value="" />
            <energyRating />
        </buildingDetails>
        <furnished />
        <auction date="" />
        <dateAvailable />
        <inspectionTimes />
        <externalLink />
        <miniweb>
            <uri id="1">http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/hamiltonhouse.htm</uri>
        </miniweb>
        <videoLink href="" />
        <objects>
            <images>
                <img id="m" modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" url="http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/images/hamiltonhouse14.jpg" format="jpg" />
            </images>
            <document />
        </objects>
    </residential>
    <residential modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" status="current">
        <agentID>012345</agentID>
        <uniqueID>13883-noosanorthshore</uniqueID>
        <isMultiple value="no" />
        <authority value="" />
        <underOffer value="no" />
        <newConstruction />
        <listingAgent id="1">
            <name />
            <telephone type="BH" />
            <telephone type="mobile" />
            <email>david@villarealestate.com.au</email>
            <twitterURL />
            <facebookURL />
            <linkedInURL />
        </listingAgent>
        <price Display="yes">3900000</price>
        <priceView />
        <address Display="yes">
            <subNumber />
            <streetNumber />
            <street>Noosa River Prime Acreage</street>
            <suburb>Noosa North Shore</suburb>
            <state>Queensland</state>
            <postcode />
            <country>AUS</country>
        </address>
        <municipality />
        <category name="AcreageSemi-rural" />
        <zone />
        <headline>"Golden Shores" Noosa North Shore</headline>
        <description><![CDATA[An incredible opportunity to develop on par with Richard Branson (your new neighbour!) Land of this calibre is very rarely offered in such a prestigious location.<br><br>Noosa North Shore is fast becoming a mecca for five-star eco-tourism development. Its enviable location makes this property an absolute winning investment & lifestyle choice.<br><br>Only 5 minutes to fabulous surf & fishing beaches, 20 minutes to iconic Hastings Street by car or 5 minutes by boat, 10 minutes to majestic Lake Cooroibah and 5 minutes to the local pub & shops.<br><br>Noosa North Shore is easily & quickly accessible by ferry from Tewantin. It is fast becoming an enviable & exclusive place to call home. Act now to make your mark on this idyllic location and develop your own signature project.<br><br>The options for development are exciting and endless – there’s ample room for luxury accommodation, tennis courts, pools, stables, helipad. There’s an existing modern, 2 bedroom holiday home with sweeping views over the river.<br><br>View: By Appointment Only<br>Price: Offers Over $3,900,000<br><br>Property Summary:<br><br>Category: Acreage Development Site<br>Bedrooms:2<br>Bathrooms:2<br>Carport:<br>Garage: Double Lockup With 3-phase power<br>Land: 60 Acres (approx)<br>Close to: Noosa, Beaches, River<br>Features: Incredible Development Site]]></description>
        <tenancy>unknown</tenancy>
        <features>
            <bedrooms>2</bedrooms>
            <Bathrooms>2</Bathrooms>
            <toilets>0</toilets>
            <ensuite>0</ensuite>
            <garages>0</garages>
            <carSpaces>0</carSpaces>
            <carports />
            <openSpaces />
            <balcony />
            <livingAreas />
            <poolInGround>0</poolInGround>
            <otherFeatures>Incredible Development Site</otherFeatures>
        </features>
        <landDetails>
            <area unit="acre">60.00</area>
        </landDetails>
        <buildingDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter" of="0.00" />
            <newlyBuilt value="" />
            <energyRating />
        </buildingDetails>
        <furnished />
        <auction date="" />
        <dateAvailable />
        <inspectionTimes />
        <externalLink />
        <miniweb>
            <uri id="1">http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/noosanorthshore.htm</uri>
        </miniweb>
        <videoLink href="" />
        <objects>
            <images>
                <img id="m" modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" url="http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/images/north_shore4.jpg" format="jpg" />
            </images>
            <document />
        </objects>
    </residential>
    <residential modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" status="current">
        <agentID>012345</agentID>
        <uniqueID>13883-balmoral</uniqueID>
        <isMultiple value="no" />
        <authority value="" />
        <underOffer value="no" />
        <newConstruction />
        <listingAgent id="1">
            <name />
            <telephone type="BH" />
            <telephone type="mobile" />
            <email>david@villarealestate.com.au</email>
            <twitterURL />
            <facebookURL />
            <linkedInURL />
        </listingAgent>
        <price Display="yes" />
        <priceView />
        <address Display="yes">
            <subNumber />
            <streetNumber />
            <street />
            <suburb>Montville</suburb>
            <state>Queensland</state>
            <postcode />
            <country>AUS</country>
        </address>
        <municipality />
        <category name="House" />
        <zone />
        <headline>"Balmoral Estate"</headline>
        <description><![CDATA[Villa Prestige Properties is very proud to introduce “Balmoral “ situated on the Sunshine Coast Blackall Range within a 5 minute walk to the quaint hinterland village of Montville. Inspired by the elegance of a European French villa and the laid-back style of an Australian country homestead, “Balmoral” inspires country charm and old fashion hospitality.<br><br>Often referred to as a place where rustic charm meets with urban comforts, this home was creatively designed by the Brisbane-based owners eight years ago who have decided to give up their precious weekend retreat due to work commitments.<br><br>This sprawling home fulfils many wishes and  can easily convert to a lavish entertaining venue; recently 80 friends were easily accommodated in the living room and veranda to enjoy a signature year of the owner Alternatively, it can comfortably switch to a more informal setting for families who can retreat to intimate spaces to share. Approvals permitting, it could even be turned into a B & B or boutique function venue for the many weddings held in the area.<br><br>In the warmer months, long lunches can be enjoyed on the 3-metre wide verandas that overlook the established gardens with small vistas to the ocean.<br><br>With its romantic charm, on several occasions brides and grooms have romantically said ‘I do’ under in the lush green surrounds offered by the property. A refreshing 12-metre salt-water pool with 12 x 6 metre loggia also offers the perfect spot to laze on summer days.<br><br>‘Balmoral’ is set on 13 undulating acres with pastures for horses to graze and shaded with macadamia trees. Peek views to the ocean to the east and to Baroon Pocket dam to the west are also a feature of the property.<br><br>The gardens take on the feel of Provence with conifers, hedging and lavender stretched along pebbled pathways; one might easily be transformed to another place and whilst picturesque, they gardens are not extensive and are easily maintained.<br><br>Also on the grounds, with its own outlook, is ‘The Rustic Red Shed', a lovely old shed that has had part of it converted into a good size two bedroom guest house whilst the other part used for its original farm duties.<br><br>There are so many features that this quality built solid home enjoys:<br><br>• 3 metre ceilings throughout<br><br>• 3 separate living areas (one with an open fire)<br><br>• Air conditioning and fans throughout<br><br>• A gourmet kitchen with 90cm gas stove and its own kitchen garden        • 5 bedrooms, 4 with ensuites<br><br>• Double lock up garage with 4 metre ceilings w/ direct home access<br><br>• A covered mudroom<br><br>• C bus system with multiple Internet and speaker points<br><br>Features on the grounds include:<br><br>• DLUG Garage + 4m x 12m carport<br><br>• 2 bedroom 85 sqm Guest House and 120 sqm work shed<br><br>• Kitchen herb gardens Various fruit trees<br><br>• Numerous paths and walkways<br><br>• Over 140,000 gallons rain water in 5 tanks<br><br>• Recycled waste water system<br><br>The beauty of this gorgeous property is not only a its gracious residence and two bedroom guest cottage and beautiful grounds., it is also just  5 mins walking distance to fine dining, boutique shopping and art galleries in the cultural village of Montville which makes it feel as though you are still in the heart of it all.<br><br>A short 20 minute trip to the coast enlightens your senses with the endless beaches that make the Sunshine coast famous adding to this, schools and Maleny hospital are also in close proximity to make life easy and Brisbane is just over a hour’s drive away.<br><br>So…… If this all sounds like a lifestyle you could immerse yourself in, please call for a discreet private inspection of this wonderful property we are so proud to represent.<br><br>View: By Appointment Only<br>Price:Price On Application<br><br>Property Summary:<br><br>Category:Landscaped Acreage Home<br>Bedrooms:5<br>Bathrooms:3<br>Garage: 3<br><br>Floorplan:Click to Load Tour<br>Land: 13 Acres (approx)<br>Close to: Hospital, Wineries, Schools<br>Features: Stables, Orchard, Gardens, Pool]]></description>
        <tenancy>unknown</tenancy>
        <features>
            <bedrooms>5</bedrooms>
            <Bathrooms>3</Bathrooms>
            <toilets>0</toilets>
            <ensuite>0</ensuite>
            <garages>0</garages>
            <carSpaces>0</carSpaces>
            <carports />
            <openSpaces />
            <balcony />
            <livingAreas />
            <poolInGround>1</poolInGround>
            <otherFeatures>Stables, Orchard, Gardens, Pool</otherFeatures>
        </features>
        <landDetails>
            <area unit="acre">13.00</area>
        </landDetails>
        <buildingDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter" of="0.00" />
            <newlyBuilt value="" />
            <energyRating />
        </buildingDetails>
        <furnished />
        <auction date="" />
        <dateAvailable />
        <inspectionTimes />
        <externalLink />
        <miniweb>
            <uri id="1">http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/balmoral.htm</uri>
        </miniweb>
        <videoLink href="" />
        <objects>
            <images>
                <img id="m" modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" url="http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/images/balmoral4.jpg" format="jpg" />
            </images>
            <document />
        </objects>
    </residential>
    <residential modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" status="current">
        <agentID>012345</agentID>
        <uniqueID>13883-cootharaba</uniqueID>
        <isMultiple value="no" />
        <authority value="" />
        <underOffer value="no" />
        <newConstruction />
        <listingAgent id="1">
            <name />
            <telephone type="BH" />
            <telephone type="mobile" />
            <email>david@villarealestate.com.au</email>
            <twitterURL />
            <facebookURL />
            <linkedInURL />
        </listingAgent>
        <price Display="yes">1875000</price>
        <priceView />
        <address Display="yes">
            <subNumber />
            <streetNumber />
            <street>Noosa North Shore Hinterland</street>
            <suburb>Cootharaba</suburb>
            <state>Queensland</state>
            <postcode />
            <country>AUS</country>
        </address>
        <municipality />
        <category name="AcreageSemi-rural" />
        <zone />
        <headline>"Cootharaba Estate" Noosa Shire</headline>
        <description><![CDATA[Build your dream home on this unique, stunning large acreage prestige property in Queensland Australia's famous, UNESCO listed, Noosa Biosphere Reserve. Enjoy the ultimate in luxury ... complete privacy.<br><br>This large prestige acreage is suitable for a private luxury estate or tourist accommodation under current Council rules. The new Sunshine Coast Regional Council and SE Queensland Land Use Plan, when implemented, will likely allow for additional dwellings on large parcels in the Shire. There is ample room for a private airstrip.<br><br>Infrastructure<br><br>The breathtaking natural features include a massive private spring fed lake (approx. a kilometer long by up to ½ kilometer wide) that sits adjacent to a Class A (pristine) wetland and spring.<br><br>Much planning and foresight has gone into the work on this beautiful piece of land. Improvements to the property include over a kilometer of properly engineered and constructed driveway (with proper drainage, crowning, crushed stone, culverts, etc.); 3 phase power; a bore; native tree plantings; landscaped entrance; new perimeter fencing with split rail entry and a large colorbond shed.<br><br>Improvements to the property have been ongoing for the past 4-5 years but the overseas owners circumstances have changed dramatically in the recent past and regrettably the property now must be sold on.<br><br>Location<br><br>The property is located within a few minutes of a 27 hole golf course and Noosa's main sailing lake with access to the Noosa River system. The world famous town of Noosa Heads, with its famous beaches, fine dining and upscale shopping is just a short drive from the property. Several lovely, small "hinterland" towns are also in very close proximity.<br><br>Money has been spent and improvements completed ... all that is needed now is your dream home to complete the picture!<br><br>Two titles are for sale: Approximately 90 acres & 180 acres<br>Offered at a very reasonable price (Approx. $8,000/acre)<br>The entire estate of approximately 280 acres is offered at AUD$2,200,000<br><br>View: By Appointment Only<br>Price: Reduced to $1,875,000<br><br>Property Summary:<br><br>Category: Acreage Development Site<br>Bedrooms: 0<br>Bathrooms: 0<br>Carport:<br>Garage: Double Lockup With 3-phase power<br>Land: 290 Acres (approx) on Two Titles<br>Close to: Noosa, Beaches<br>Features: Incredible Home Site]]></description>
        <tenancy>unknown</tenancy>
        <features>
            <bedrooms>0</bedrooms>
            <Bathrooms />
            <toilets>0</toilets>
            <ensuite>0</ensuite>
            <garages>0</garages>
            <carSpaces>0</carSpaces>
            <carports />
            <openSpaces />
            <balcony />
            <livingAreas />
            <poolInGround>0</poolInGround>
            <otherFeatures>Incredible Home Site</otherFeatures>
        </features>
        <landDetails>
            <area unit="acre">290.00</area>
        </landDetails>
        <buildingDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter" of="0.00" />
            <newlyBuilt value="" />
            <energyRating />
        </buildingDetails>
        <furnished />
        <auction date="" />
        <dateAvailable />
        <inspectionTimes />
        <externalLink />
        <miniweb>
            <uri id="1">http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/cootharaba.htm</uri>
        </miniweb>
        <videoLink href="" />
        <objects>
            <images>
                <img id="m" modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" url="http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/images/cootharaba5_000.jpg" format="jpg" />
            </images>
            <document />
        </objects>
    </residential>
    <residential modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" status="current">
        <agentID>012345</agentID>
        <uniqueID>13883-coastview</uniqueID>
        <isMultiple value="no" />
        <authority value="" />
        <underOffer value="no" />
        <newConstruction />
        <listingAgent id="1">
            <name />
            <telephone type="BH" />
            <telephone type="mobile" />
            <email>david@villarealestate.com.au</email>
            <twitterURL />
            <facebookURL />
            <linkedInURL />
        </listingAgent>
        <price Display="yes">2950000</price>
        <priceView />
        <address Display="yes">
            <subNumber />
            <streetNumber>54</streetNumber>
            <street>Coast View Parade</street>
            <suburb>Doonan</suburb>
            <state>Queensland</state>
            <postcode />
            <country>AUS</country>
        </address>
        <municipality />
        <category name="House" />
        <zone />
        <headline>Architectural Hilltop Luxury Doonan, Qld</headline>
        <description><![CDATA[Crowning the ridge, looking over the majestic hinterland towards Noosa Heads, this regal residence is one befitting royalty. Set on two lush acres, your castle in the sky awaits.<br><br>A luxurious, contemporary and comfortable, architecturally designed single level residence exudes refinement sparing no expense. The very private residence is located on an elevated two acre parcel, optimally positioned to afford expansive views from Noosa North Shore to Coolum Beach.<br><br>Elegant water features are incorporated into the floor plan, immediately evident as you enter the home across limestone pavers into the open foyer. You are met with views out to the central pool courtyard that serves as the central focus of the home.<br><br>The main wing of the residence consists of a large office, ensuited guest bedroom, large kitchen and dining room, and master bedroom which is also ensuited. All rooms on this end of the home open on to the gardens and amazing views via timber folding doors.<br><br>The opposite wing of the home is made up of lounge room, laundry and another massive bedroom and ensuite. The bedroom and lounge both open onto the pool and covered pergola, offering a peaceful place for taking in the sun.<br><br>From the terrace, look out over the infinity-edge pool to the majesty of Noosa Heads and the Sunshine Coast. The sub-tropical gardens are elegant and easily cared for with a minimum of maintenance required.<br><br>This magnificent residence is perfect for the executive or professional for whom only the very best will do. Call us now to arrange a private inspection of the property.<br><br>A list of features and benefits:<br><br>* Architect designed , perfect for entertaining indoors and out<br>* 3 bedrooms each with ensuite and private robes<br>* Expansive living areas<br>* Wet edge swimming pool taking in the panoramic coastal and hinterland views<br>* A kitchen fit for a chef featuring stainless Meile appliances<br>* Extremely high cyclone rating in its construction<br>* Total privacy, absolutely secure, complete piece of mind!<br>* Panoramic Views cannot be built out<br>* Land comprises bush reserve with wallabies, bandicoots and bird life<br>* Bird attracting trees and bushes planted<br>* Secure Gated Residence with Intercom system<br>* All timber is a hardwood - New Guinea Rosewood<br>* Timber in Doors and windows are 50ml thick<br>* All glass is toughened and tinted<br>* All rooms have French or bi-fold doors<br>* All doors and windows are 2.7M<br>* All ceilings 3M high<br>* Windows designed to capture earliest morning and latest afternoon sun<br>* House designed to maximise summer breezes from all aspects<br>* All bedrooms have overhead fans<br>* Discreet placement of louvre windows ensures breezes when doors shut<br>* Louvre windows all have rated fire screens<br>* Surround sound throughout house and in entertainment areas<br>* Stone feature walls - craftsman laid<br>* Reverse cycle air conditioning and heating<br>* Electric blinds in bedrooms one and two<br>* Back to Base alarm system facility available<br>* Every plant on property connected to automatic irrigation system<br>* Low maintenance home<br>* Established vegetable garden and fruit trees<br>* Bore water<br>* Full garden/courtyard mood lighting<br>* 96,000 litres of tank water<br>* Tank water inter connectible with bore system<br>* Carbon filter on tanks<br>* Pool heating (heat pump) low tariff electricity<br>* Pool filtration also on low tariff<br>* Full drinking water filtration system in the house/refrigerator<br>* Instant over sink boiling water<br>* Separate pet compound<br>* All floors/bathrooms (to ceiling) vitrified tiles.<br>* 3 car garage<br>* 3 bedrooms, all have own ensuites (1 with full bath as well as separate shower)<br>* Visitor parking bay provided<br>* Study with walk-in storage room<br>* Sweeping views from Mt Cooroy to North Shore/Noosa south to Coolum<br><br>View: By Appointment Only<br>Price: $2,950,000<br><br>Property Summary:<br><br>Category: Executive Acreage<br>Bedrooms:3<br>Bathrooms:4<br>Garage: Triple<br><br>Floorplan:Click to Load Tour<br>Land: 2 Acres (approx)<br>Close to: Noosa, Beaches, Schools<br>Features: Infinity Pool, Architectural Design,Tropical Gardens]]></description>
        <tenancy>unknown</tenancy>
        <features>
            <bedrooms>3</bedrooms>
            <Bathrooms>4</Bathrooms>
            <toilets>0</toilets>
            <ensuite>0</ensuite>
            <garages>0</garages>
            <carSpaces>0</carSpaces>
            <carports />
            <openSpaces />
            <balcony />
            <livingAreas />
            <poolInGround>1</poolInGround>
            <otherFeatures>Infinity Pool, Architectural Design, Tropical Gardens</otherFeatures>
        </features>
        <landDetails>
            <area unit="acre">2.00</area>
        </landDetails>
        <buildingDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter" of="0.00" />
            <newlyBuilt value="" />
            <energyRating />
        </buildingDetails>
        <furnished />
        <auction date="" />
        <dateAvailable />
        <inspectionTimes />
        <externalLink />
        <miniweb>
            <uri id="1">http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/coastview.htm</uri>
        </miniweb>
        <videoLink href="" />
        <objects>
            <images>
                <img id="m" modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" url="http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/images/coast_view23.jpg" format="jpg" />
            </images>
            <document />
        </objects>
    </residential>
    <residential modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" status="current">
        <agentID>012345</agentID>
        <uniqueID>13883-flametree</uniqueID>
        <isMultiple value="no" />
        <authority value="" />
        <underOffer value="no" />
        <newConstruction />
        <listingAgent id="1">
            <name />
            <telephone type="BH" />
            <telephone type="mobile" />
            <email>david@villarealestate.com.au</email>
            <twitterURL />
            <facebookURL />
            <linkedInURL />
        </listingAgent>
        <price Display="yes">1150000</price>
        <priceView />
        <address Display="yes">
            <subNumber />
            <streetNumber />
            <street />
            <suburb>$1</suburb>
            <state>000 (Aud)</state>
            <postcode />
            <country>AUS</country>
        </address>
        <municipality />
        <category name="AcreageSemi-rural" />
        <zone />
        <headline>Flametree Park Equestrian Ready Eudlo, Qld</headline>
        <description><![CDATA[Flametree Park is a property ideal for a family wanting a peaceful rural lifestyle while still being centrally located to everything the Sunshine Coast has to offer.  Set on 16 acres, the property features an Olympic sized riding arena, stables, and riding tracks.<br><br>The three large paddocks have been rested for three years and include automatic water feeds and horse friendly fencing. Stable block includes two stables with lights and fans plus drive through float carport. Separate 6 x 6m lockable shed and wash bay.<br><br>The master-built family home has high ceilings and quality fittings. Four king size bedrooms with BIR, large study with built in timber bookcase, large modern kitchen and 2.5 bathrooms. Reverse cycle air conditioning and fans throughout the house add to the comforts, along with the added benefit of solar hot water.<br><br>Flametree Park offers complete privacy while being close to everything a family could need. Ten minutes to private schools, shops and the Sunshine Coast University, and 20 minutes to beautiful Sunshine Coast beaches. Brisbane International airport is only an hour away.<br><br>This much loved 12 year old home has seen many happy times. Now that the kids have grown up, it's time to let another family enjoy the wonderful lifestyle offered by the property.<br><br>Please call for a private inspection or come to one of our open for inspections to view this lovely family home. Contact Linda Shore-Perez at 0427 378 687 or by email.<br><br>View:Open For Inspection Sat 16 Aug 12pm - 1pm<br>Price: $1,150,000<br><br>Property Summary:<br><br>Category: House<br>Bedrooms:4<br>Bathrooms:3<br>Carport:2<br>Floorplan: Click Here to View<br>Land: 2282.00sqm (approx)<br>Close to: Schools, Transport, Beaches<br>Features: Ensuite, A/C, Paddocks]]></description>
        <tenancy>unknown</tenancy>
        <features>
            <bedrooms>4</bedrooms>
            <Bathrooms>3</Bathrooms>
            <toilets>0</toilets>
            <ensuite>0</ensuite>
            <garages>0</garages>
            <carSpaces>0</carSpaces>
            <carports />
            <openSpaces />
            <balcony />
            <livingAreas />
            <poolInGround>0</poolInGround>
            <otherFeatures>Ensuite, A/C, Paddocks</otherFeatures>
        </features>
        <landDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter">2282.00</area>
        </landDetails>
        <buildingDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter" of="0.00" />
            <newlyBuilt value="" />
            <energyRating />
        </buildingDetails>
        <furnished />
        <auction date="" />
        <dateAvailable />
        <inspectionTimes />
        <externalLink />
        <miniweb>
            <uri id="1">http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/flametree.htm</uri>
        </miniweb>
        <videoLink href="" />
        <objects>
            <images />
            <document />
        </objects>
    </residential>
    <residential modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" status="current">
        <agentID>012345</agentID>
        <uniqueID>13883-frogmouth</uniqueID>
        <isMultiple value="no" />
        <authority value="" />
        <underOffer value="no" />
        <newConstruction />
        <listingAgent id="1">
            <name />
            <telephone type="BH" />
            <telephone type="mobile" />
            <email>david@villarealestate.com.au</email>
            <twitterURL />
            <facebookURL />
            <linkedInURL />
        </listingAgent>
        <price Display="yes">1850000</price>
        <priceView />
        <address Display="yes">
            <subNumber />
            <streetNumber>74</streetNumber>
            <street>Frogmouth Lane</street>
            <suburb>Lake MacDonald</suburb>
            <state>Queensland</state>
            <postcode />
            <country>AUS</country>
        </address>
        <municipality />
        <category name="House" />
        <zone />
        <headline>Queenslander on Acreage Lake MacDonald, Qld</headline>
        <description><![CDATA[Are you looking for that perfect setting to create the ultimate Queensland lifestyle? Look no further than Frogmouth Lane in Cooroy. This stunning 38 acre parcel is ideal as a horse or hobby farm property with paddocks and a beautiful running creek. Just minutes from historic Eumundi, Cooroy and Noosa’s glorious beaches, immerse yourself in the beauty of this part of the world.<br><br>Set at the end of a quiet country lane, the home is situated to take advantage of the glorious weather and scenic position. Rooms are light and spacious and the living room opens out to the large deck which is ideal for entertaining & al fresco meals. The homesports a lovely pool and sunning platform, as well as separate garage and two-room studio.<br><br>The unique property boasts multiple paddocks, a round yard, tack room and two permanent, spring-fed dams. Enjoy as a family home or as a potential business venture.<br><br>Don’t miss your opportunity to purchase an easy care estate of 38 peaceful, private and picturesque acres positioned at the end of a blue chip lane. Experience the joy and serenity. Call us today to inspect!<br><br>View:On Appointment<br>Price:$1,850,000<br><br>Property Summary:<br><br>Category: Luxury Acreage Home<br>Bedrooms:6<br>Bathrooms:4<br>Garage:2<br>Land: 38 acres (approx)<br>Close to: Beaches, Village, Noosa<br>Features: Pool, Creek, Views, Fenced]]></description>
        <tenancy>unknown</tenancy>
        <features>
            <bedrooms>6</bedrooms>
            <Bathrooms>4</Bathrooms>
            <toilets>0</toilets>
            <ensuite>0</ensuite>
            <garages>0</garages>
            <carSpaces>0</carSpaces>
            <carports />
            <openSpaces />
            <balcony />
            <livingAreas />
            <poolInGround>1</poolInGround>
            <otherFeatures>Pool, Creek, Views, Fenced</otherFeatures>
        </features>
        <landDetails>
            <area unit="acre">38.00</area>
        </landDetails>
        <buildingDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter" of="0.00" />
            <newlyBuilt value="" />
            <energyRating />
        </buildingDetails>
        <furnished />
        <auction date="" />
        <dateAvailable />
        <inspectionTimes />
        <externalLink />
        <miniweb>
            <uri id="1">http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/frogmouth.htm</uri>
        </miniweb>
        <videoLink href="" />
        <objects>
            <images>
                <img id="m" modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" url="http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/images/frogmouth5.jpg" format="jpg" />
            </images>
            <document />
        </objects>
    </residential>
    <residential modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" status="current">
        <agentID>012345</agentID>
        <uniqueID>13883-vantagelot2</uniqueID>
        <isMultiple value="no" />
        <authority value="" />
        <underOffer value="no" />
        <newConstruction />
        <listingAgent id="1">
            <name />
            <telephone type="BH" />
            <telephone type="mobile" />
            <email>david@villarealestate.com.au</email>
            <twitterURL />
            <facebookURL />
            <linkedInURL />
        </listingAgent>
        <price Display="yes" />
        <priceView />
        <address Display="yes">
            <subNumber />
            <streetNumber />
            <street />
            <suburb>Coolum Beach</suburb>
            <state>Queensland</state>
            <postcode />
            <country>AUS</country>
        </address>
        <municipality />
        <category name="House" />
        <zone />
        <headline>Coolum Resort &amp; Spa/ Lot 2 Vantage</headline>
        <description><![CDATA[Sophisticated "Soho" Loft !!!<br>That was the brief given to Architect Georgina Beckett when commissioned to design this fabulous home within the grounds of the Coolum Resort & Spa, formerly Hyatt Regency Coolum.<br><br>Plenty of space for art, light filled spaces, high ceilings and great entertaining areas were also the criteria given, as must haves to the Architect. So to work she went, creating not only architectural brilliance but also a home that has spaces to suit every need and everyone!<br><br>This gorgeous home of over 400 sqm has four bedrooms, three bathrooms, separate family room and a kitchen, living and dining that open out to an undercover entertaining area and pool. There is a huge garage with loads of storage and room for your golf buggy. This home is finished with the quality you would expect from a house of this caliber, timber, Shellstone, and pure wool carpets are used for flooring. Grohe and Villeroy & Boch fixtures compliment designer basins in the bathrooms. A massive custom designed kitchen with butlers pantry and bifold windows compliment the design and style of this home.<br><br>So it is established that the house is fabulous, add to this the bonuses that comes with living at Coolum Resort & Spa, and you have an instantly an amazing lifestyle!<br><br>The Coolum Resort is Sunshine Coasts absolute best kept secret! Imagine... driving your buggy to the beautiful white sandy beaches and going for a walk or a dip. Enjoying dinner at one of the resorts 5 restaurants without getting in your car. Making your life a healthy one with a world class day spa and gymnasium that includes a 25 meter lap pool, Jacuzzis, steam rooms, saunas, state of the art gym and classes including Tai Chi and golf conditioning.<br><br>What the resort is famous for is GOLF! The resort has been home to the Australian PGA for many years. The magnificent 18 hole championship golf course, including a practice golf range and practice putting greens, are all part of your backyard to enjoy every day of the year.<br><br>Living within the grounds of the Coolum Resort & Spa also gets you to meet new friends! With social member functions as well as numerous gala events, balls and festivals you can chose to be as social as you wish, all of this is included with low body corporate fees (under $2,000 per annum and membership starting at $750) you really are not just choosing a stunning home in a beautiful location, you are choosing a quality of life.<br><br>If you are looking for a permanent change or a time out from your hectic schedule you will not regret what this home has to offer. I invite you for an inspection today for a viewing of this incredible home offered at an incredible price!!!!<br><br>Living within this Exclusive “Vantage” Enclave provides you with:<br><br>• Resort Membership<br>• Full Gymnasium, Yoga and aerobics classes<br>• Exclusive Sun Spa with massage<br><br>• Full beauty treatments and hairdressers<br>• Tennis courts and club house<br>• 25% Discount on golf course fees<br>• Culinary options with 5 different restaurants<br>• Buggy rights to drive throughout the resort<br>• Direct Beach Access to miles of white sandy beaches<br><br>• Room Service if you do not wish to cook<br>• Catering if you are entertaining guests<br>• Dog permissible<br><br>View: On Appointment<br>Price:Price on Application<br><br>Property Summary:<br><br>Category: Luxury Resort Home<br>Bedrooms: 4<br>Bathrooms: 3<br>Garage: 3<br><br>Floor Plan:Click to Load Tour<br>Land: 850 sqm (approx)<br>Close to: Beaches, Resort, Airport<br>Features: Pool, A/C, Golf & Spa, Gated]]></description>
        <tenancy>unknown</tenancy>
        <features>
            <bedrooms>4</bedrooms>
            <Bathrooms>3</Bathrooms>
            <toilets>0</toilets>
            <ensuite>0</ensuite>
            <garages>0</garages>
            <carSpaces>0</carSpaces>
            <carports />
            <openSpaces />
            <balcony />
            <livingAreas />
            <poolInGround>1</poolInGround>
            <otherFeatures>Pool, A/C, Golf &amp; Spa, Gated</otherFeatures>
        </features>
        <landDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter">850.00</area>
        </landDetails>
        <buildingDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter" of="0.00" />
            <newlyBuilt value="" />
            <energyRating />
        </buildingDetails>
        <furnished />
        <auction date="" />
        <dateAvailable />
        <inspectionTimes />
        <externalLink />
        <miniweb>
            <uri id="1">http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/vantagelot2.htm</uri>
        </miniweb>
        <videoLink href="" />
        <objects>
            <images>
                <img id="m" modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" url="http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/images/lot2vantage13.jpg" format="jpg" />
            </images>
            <document />
        </objects>
    </residential>
    <residential modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" status="current">
        <agentID>012345</agentID>
        <uniqueID>13883-hiddenvalley</uniqueID>
        <isMultiple value="no" />
        <authority value="" />
        <underOffer value="no" />
        <newConstruction />
        <listingAgent id="1">
            <name />
            <telephone type="BH" />
            <telephone type="mobile" />
            <email>david@villarealestate.com.au</email>
            <twitterURL />
            <facebookURL />
            <linkedInURL />
        </listingAgent>
        <price Display="yes">1449000</price>
        <priceView />
        <address Display="yes">
            <subNumber />
            <streetNumber />
            <street />
            <suburb>Eumundi</suburb>
            <state>Queensland</state>
            <postcode />
            <country>AUS</country>
        </address>
        <municipality />
        <category name="House" />
        <zone />
        <headline>"Hidden Valley" In Your Future Eumundi, Qld</headline>
        <description><![CDATA[A once in a life time opportunity exists to purchase not only a magnificent Queenslander on just under 4 beautiful acres but also along with it an outstanding income potential.<br><br>Situated in the heart of Eumundi this hopelessly romantic 1895 Queenslander and a funky 1940’s railway carriage overlook 4 tranquil acres of orchard, lake, bridge and bounds the North Maroochy River.<br><br>This property truly has limitless opportunities and its listed price represents great value, simply as a beautiful family home on serene acreage 5 mins walk to town, but additionally, ,with its commercial kitchen license and Bed and Breakfast license, running with great success, it also provides a great lifestyle opportunity offering a fabulous income.<br><br>The unique opportunity of Hidden Valley is that you can make it into whatever you want. Whether you book it out fully as a B&B, turn it into a Tea House on Eumundi Market days, open an Art or Antiques gallery, or just rent the railway carriage rooms for a passive income… the choices are limitless.<br><br>This gracious old Queenslander was moved from Brisbane many years ago and features Art Nouveau details of that era like 13 foot decorative stamped tin ceilings, wide board flooring, large wraparound verandahs and a magnificent full height, lead lighted entry.  At this time it was completely refurbished including plumbing, electrical, roofing, etc.<br><br>The grand dining, with open fire, is the heart of the home that leads onto the living room with spectacular views over the grounds. Off the magnificent entry foyer there are 3 large bedrooms with ensuites, all with their own sense of unique character for guests and also a separate managers bedroom and ensuite. The inviting "Big Red" kitchen is capable of handling the largest of gatherings, and separate office and laundry a necessity for smooth running of operations.<br><br>The romantic railway carriage also has two bedrooms with ensuites and makes any getaway more fun.<br><br>My favourite part, however, is the wide verandahs with the cozy wicker furniture, perfect to take in the beauty over the valley and lose oneself on a lazy afternoon.<br><br>This really is a must see property that not only represents a unique piece of history in one of the most beautiful places in the world, but also a great monetary value in its capacity to supply an income. If this sounds like the life you've been dreaming of!<br><br>For further photos and information a browse through the website www.eumundibed.com is a must.<br><br>Properties like this do not remain long in the market, so please contact me for an early private inspection or alternatively, we invite you to join us Sunday, May 18th for an Open House and tea on the verandah.<br><br>Linda Shore-Perez for a private inspection on 0427 378 687<br><br>View:On Appointment<br>Price: Offers Over $1,449,000<br><br>Property Summary:<br><br>Category: House<br>Bedrooms:6<br>Bathrooms:6<br>Floorplan:Click Here To View Floorplan<br>Carport: Double<br>Land:4 Acres (approx)<br>Close to: Markets, Noosa<br>Features: Commercial Kitchen, A/C, Potential Income]]></description>
        <tenancy>unknown</tenancy>
        <features>
            <bedrooms>6</bedrooms>
            <Bathrooms>6</Bathrooms>
            <toilets>0</toilets>
            <ensuite>0</ensuite>
            <garages>0</garages>
            <carSpaces>0</carSpaces>
            <carports />
            <openSpaces />
            <balcony />
            <livingAreas />
            <poolInGround>0</poolInGround>
            <otherFeatures>Commercial Kitchen, A/C, Potential Income</otherFeatures>
        </features>
        <landDetails>
            <area unit="acre">4.00</area>
        </landDetails>
        <buildingDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter" of="0.00" />
            <newlyBuilt value="" />
            <energyRating />
        </buildingDetails>
        <furnished />
        <auction date="" />
        <dateAvailable />
        <inspectionTimes />
        <externalLink />
        <miniweb>
            <uri id="1">http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/hiddenvalley.htm</uri>
        </miniweb>
        <videoLink href="" />
        <objects>
            <images>
                <img id="m" modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" url="http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/images/hiddenvalley2.jpg" format="jpg" />
            </images>
            <document />
        </objects>
    </residential>
    <residential modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" status="current">
        <agentID>012345</agentID>
        <uniqueID>13883-vantagelot3</uniqueID>
        <isMultiple value="no" />
        <authority value="" />
        <underOffer value="no" />
        <newConstruction>NEW</newConstruction>
        <listingAgent id="1">
            <name />
            <telephone type="BH" />
            <telephone type="mobile" />
            <email>david@villarealestate.com.au</email>
            <twitterURL />
            <facebookURL />
            <linkedInURL />
        </listingAgent>
        <price Display="yes">1000000</price>
        <priceView />
        <address Display="yes">
            <subNumber />
            <streetNumber>3</streetNumber>
            <street>Bonment Road</street>
            <suburb>Yaroomba</suburb>
            <state>Queensland</state>
            <postcode />
            <country>AUS</country>
        </address>
        <municipality />
        <category name="House" />
        <zone />
        <headline>Coolum Resort &amp; Spa / Lot 3 Vantage</headline>
        <description><![CDATA[The builder did not spare any expense on the finishes of this new home! This spectacular, multi-level residence is located inside the gates of the Coolum Resort's most recent release. "Vantage" is a community<br>within the Coolum Resort & Spa that provides convenient access<br>to the resort facilities whilst offering an enviable lifestyle. The design of this community preserves the natural character of the site and aims to maximise views from within Vantage.<br><br>One of Australia's most coveted coastal adresses, your new resort<br>dream home is positioned to take full advantage of all the resort has<br>on offer. From your golf buggy as you drive to the first tee, maybe grab<br>a hot cappuccino at one of the Village cafés. Keep driving to the beach pool for a swim and a surf along Yaroomba's pristine beaches, patrolled every day of the year. All this and never getting on a public roadway!<br>You see, along with membership rights to this world class resort<br>are buggy access from your front door throughout the entire resort.<br><br>This contemporary, custom built home embellishes the five star lifestyle<br>sought after at Coolum Resort & Spa. The highest construction standards and finishes of this beautiful home include natural stone benchtops, european fixtures and appliances, three generous bedrooms, en suite plus a main bathrooms and downstairs powder, two separate living areas, high ceilings, two-pac cabnetry, a large 10m x 3.5m pool with wet edge and, of course, the standards air conditioning and security alarm system.<br><br>The elevated 600+ sqm is a choice parcel within the release,<br>positioned to take in views of the golf course from the upstairs balcony.<br>The secure gated community borders several of the opening<br>holes of the newly renovated PGA Championship golf course.<br>A lifestyle opportunity is at your fingertips once you take adVantage<br>of this beautiful, new designer home.<br><br>Living within this Exclusive “Vantage” Enclave provides you with:<br><br>• Resort Membership<br>• Full Gymnasium, Yoga and aerobics classes<br>• Exclusive Sun Spa with massage<br><br>• Full beauty treatments and hairdressers<br>• Tennis courts and club house<br>• 25% Discount on golf course fees<br>• Culinary options with 5 different restaurants<br>• Buggy rights to drive throughout the resort<br>• Direct Beach Access to miles of white sandy beaches<br><br>• Room Service if you do not wish to cook<br>• Catering if you are entertaining guests<br>• Dog permissible<br><br>So what are you waiting for? With the Sunshine Coast's magnificent climate and airport only 10 minutes away, this property is a sound investment as well as an ideal lifestyle.<br><br>View: On Appointment<br>Price: Offers Over $1,000,000<br><br>Property Summary:<br><br>Category: Contemporary Resort Home<br>Bedrooms:4 (3 + Study)<br>Bathrooms:3<br>Garage: 2+ Buggy<br><br>Floor Plan:Click to Load Tour<br>Land: 670 sqm (approx)<br>Close to: Beaches, Resort, Airport<br>Features: Pool, A/C, Security, Gated Community]]></description>
        <tenancy>unknown</tenancy>
        <features>
            <bedrooms>4</bedrooms>
            <Bathrooms>3</Bathrooms>
            <toilets>0</toilets>
            <ensuite>0</ensuite>
            <garages>0</garages>
            <carSpaces>0</carSpaces>
            <carports />
            <openSpaces />
            <balcony>yes</balcony>
            <livingAreas />
            <poolInGround>1</poolInGround>
            <otherFeatures>Pool, A/C, Security, Gated Community</otherFeatures>
        </features>
        <landDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter">670.00</area>
        </landDetails>
        <buildingDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter" of="0.00" />
            <newlyBuilt value="NEW" />
            <energyRating />
        </buildingDetails>
        <furnished />
        <auction date="" />
        <dateAvailable />
        <inspectionTimes />
        <externalLink />
        <miniweb>
            <uri id="1">http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/vantagelot3.htm</uri>
        </miniweb>
        <videoLink href="" />
        <objects>
            <images>
                <img id="m" modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" url="http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/images/aerial_000.jpg" format="jpg" />
            </images>
            <document />
        </objects>
    </residential>
    <residential modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" status="current">
        <agentID>012345</agentID>
        <uniqueID>13883-fourwinds</uniqueID>
        <isMultiple value="no" />
        <authority value="" />
        <underOffer value="no" />
        <newConstruction />
        <listingAgent id="1">
            <name />
            <telephone type="BH" />
            <telephone type="mobile" />
            <email>david@villarealestate.com.au</email>
            <twitterURL />
            <facebookURL />
            <linkedInURL />
        </listingAgent>
        <price Display="yes">4500000</price>
        <priceView />
        <address Display="yes">
            <subNumber />
            <streetNumber>448</streetNumber>
            <street>Old Byron Bay Road</street>
            <suburb>Byron Bay</suburb>
            <state>New South Wales</state>
            <postcode />
            <country>AUS</country>
        </address>
        <municipality />
        <category name="House" />
        <zone />
        <headline>"Four Winds Estate" Byron Bay, NSW</headline>
        <description><![CDATA[Absolutely one of the most exciting and prestigious properties to come on the coastal market in a long, long time, we proudly offer "Four Winds Estate." The elevated escarpment position lifts you above the beauty and grandeur of the Byron Bay coastline and begs the question, "What more could you want?"<br><br>This seven acre (2.73 ha) estate sits above the the coastal fringe behind Broken Head and the picturesque beauty of this tropical oasis creates a property unmatched on today's market. The long drive gently brings the visitor up through expansive lawns and past the newly built stables and equestrian arena to the main residence.<br><br>Infrastructure<br><br>The buildings on the property have been designed to the highest standards with the main emphasis placed on integrating the indoor/outdoor lifestyle the region offers. With cathedral ceilings and the stone finishings throughout, you can't help but feel part of a five-star spa resort.<br><br>Timer floors and fine marble appointments add to the casual elegance on exhibit. Reverse cycle air conditioning, though rarely needed, is ducted throughout.  A warm open fireplace (glass of red optional) whenever the need strikes.<br><br>The lagoon-style swimming pool, resplendant with spa and waterfall are central to the amazing tropical gardens that surround the property. Meander throughout the magneficent grounds and revel to the sounds of the abundant native wildlife.<br><br>Location<br><br>Commanding a breathtaking coastal and hinterland panorama, Four Winds Estate and villas are the ultimate escape, just 10 minutes from Byron Bay.  Truely one of the world's premiere coastal destinations, Byron Bay is renowned for its beautiful surf beaches. It is the place where the temperate and tropical waters merge, making it a popular area for scuba diving and snorkelling.<br><br>Byron Bay is located 759 km north of Sydney and 140 km south of Brisbane. Cape Byron, a headland adjacent to the town, is the most easterly point of Australia. Click here to view on googlemaps.<br><br>View: By Appointment Only<br>Price:$4,500,000<br><br>Property Summary:<br><br>Category: Main House and 2 Guest Villas<br>Bedrooms: 5<br>Bathrooms: 5<br>Carport:<br>Garage: Double<br>Land: 6 Acres (approx)<br>Close to: Byron Bay, Beaches, Schools<br>Features: New pool, stables and arena, tropical gardens]]></description>
        <tenancy>unknown</tenancy>
        <features>
            <bedrooms>5</bedrooms>
            <Bathrooms>5</Bathrooms>
            <toilets>0</toilets>
            <ensuite>0</ensuite>
            <garages>0</garages>
            <carSpaces>0</carSpaces>
            <carports />
            <openSpaces />
            <balcony />
            <livingAreas />
            <poolInGround>1</poolInGround>
            <otherFeatures>New pool, stables and arena, tropical gardens</otherFeatures>
        </features>
        <landDetails>
            <area unit="acre">6.00</area>
        </landDetails>
        <buildingDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter" of="0.00" />
            <newlyBuilt value="" />
            <energyRating />
        </buildingDetails>
        <furnished />
        <auction date="" />
        <dateAvailable />
        <inspectionTimes />
        <externalLink />
        <miniweb>
            <uri id="1">http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/fourwinds.htm</uri>
        </miniweb>
        <videoLink href="" />
        <objects>
            <images>
                <img id="m" modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" url="http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/images/4windsaerial.jpg" format="jpg" />
            </images>
            <document />
        </objects>
    </residential>
    <residential modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" status="current">
        <agentID>012345</agentID>
        <uniqueID>13883-finleyroad</uniqueID>
        <isMultiple value="no" />
        <authority value="" />
        <underOffer value="no" />
        <newConstruction />
        <listingAgent id="1">
            <name />
            <telephone type="BH" />
            <telephone type="mobile" />
            <email>david@villarealestate.com.au</email>
            <twitterURL />
            <facebookURL />
            <linkedInURL />
        </listingAgent>
        <price Display="yes">2600000</price>
        <priceView />
        <address Display="yes">
            <subNumber />
            <streetNumber>21</streetNumber>
            <street>Finley Road</street>
            <suburb>Eumundi</suburb>
            <state>Queensland</state>
            <postcode />
            <country>AUS</country>
        </address>
        <municipality />
        <category name="House" />
        <zone />
        <headline>"The Knoll"</headline>
        <description><![CDATA[Do you picture yourself living in a five star country residence, high upon your own private Knoll surrounded by breathtaking views in every direction.<br><br>Then welcome home to "The Knoll", a contemporary two-story designer home perched atop a beautiful rise. Epitomising all that constitutes country elegance, with white post and rail fencing set on over 10 acres of rolling pasture that is bordered on the south by the North Maroochy River, it is a perfect location for horses or a few head of cattle.<br><br>Entry to the property via a quiet country lane and a 250 metre bitumen, tree lined driveway that leads you up to this magnificent grand residence.<br><br>Once inside, your senses are greeted with light, space and some of the finest finishes imaginable. The stunning entry and water-feature leads into the foyer with grand staircase. Two generous bedrooms on the ground level with a shared ensuite near the front of the home on your left, another pair of bedrooms with adjoining ensuite past the stairs on your right. Not to mention the enormous media room with projection television and ultra-­modern Sonos sound system, massive laundry and a smaller more intimate TV room.<br><br>The family chef will not be disappointed when they see what awaits. A large stone benchtop island with seating for six surrounds a massive workspace with the latest Aga cooker, stainless appliances and an enormous walk-­in pantry. The dining and living areas that adjoin the kitchen look out to the 25 metre junior Olympic size, three-­lane pool with jacuzzi. Just off the pool are covered verandah and entertaining courtyard and pool room that could be used as an office or gymnasium.<br><br>Up the circular stairway, you will find a dedicated, spacious master suite. This is a place where you can get away from it all and enjoy the sweeping views from your covered balcony, or simply relax in the marble finished ensuite. There is also a study/office or second master dressing room adjacent to the bedroom to complete this luxurious retreat.<br><br>From a practical standpoint, water is not an issue with storage capacity of 20,000 gallons supplied from two concrete tanks, and solar hot-­water capacity of 435 litres. The large dam on the property supplies water to ring the main garden area surrounds. The property is fully fenced, with a large dog-proof house paddock. There is an electronic entry gate at front. There is also an American style Barn suitable for holding farm equipment.<br><br>The elevated property is truly one of a kind, sporting 360 degree hinterland views. The southern edge of the parcel enjoys over 200 meters of north Maroochy river frontage highlighted by lush and pristine rainforest and even a resident platypus! If a return to nature is what you are searching for, your search is over.<br><br>This stunning home has too many options to list and must be seen to be believed.<br><br>Located just 1 km to the historic country town of Eumundi and its famous craft markets, 15 minutes to the pristine beaches of Noosa with some of Australia's best restaurants and an easy drive to Brisbane of just over an hour.<br><br>Please contact our office to arrange an inspection of this exceptional property and, rather than dreaming to live, live the dream.<br><br>Price: $2,600,000<br><br>Property Summary:<br><br>Category: Hilltop Acreage Estate<br>Bedrooms:5<br>Bathrooms:3 + 2 powder<br>Carport:<br>Garage: Double<br>Land: 10 Acres (approx)<br>Close to: Noosa, Beaches, Schools, Transport<br>Features: Huge pool, barn, fully-fenced]]></description>
        <tenancy>unknown</tenancy>
        <features>
            <bedrooms>5</bedrooms>
            <Bathrooms>3</Bathrooms>
            <toilets>0</toilets>
            <ensuite>0</ensuite>
            <garages>0</garages>
            <carSpaces>0</carSpaces>
            <carports />
            <openSpaces />
            <balcony>yes</balcony>
            <livingAreas />
            <poolInGround>1</poolInGround>
            <otherFeatures>Huge pool, barn, fully-fenced</otherFeatures>
        </features>
        <landDetails>
            <area unit="acre">10.00</area>
        </landDetails>
        <buildingDetails>
            <area unit="squareMeter" of="0.00" />
            <newlyBuilt value="" />
            <energyRating />
        </buildingDetails>
        <furnished />
        <auction date="" />
        <dateAvailable />
        <inspectionTimes />
        <externalLink />
        <miniweb>
            <uri id="1">http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/finleyroad.htm</uri>
        </miniweb>
        <videoLink href="" />
        <objects>
            <images>
                <img id="m" modTime="2014-08-31-00:52:19" url="http://www.villarealestate.com.au/listing/images/finley_new10.jpg" format="jpg" />
            </images>
            <document />
        </objects>
    </residential>
</propertyList>